▍2026 辛辛那提 WTA1000 第二轮
诺斯科娃 6-3 6-3 布尔特 · 赛后场上采访
comes out, breaks you early
她一上来就破了你的发球
but you obviously figured something out.
但你显然找到了办法
What was the adjustment you made?
你做了什么调整
It was just probably the mental state.
大概就是心态吧
You know, it's never easy to start a match.
开局从来都不容易
You know
你知道
to be a break down immediately
一上来就被破发
and then have to get back into the match.
然后还得把自己拉回比赛里
Katie, she's a great player.
凯蒂是很好的球员
I knew it was going to be tough,
我知道这场会难打
especially at the beginning.
尤其是开头
So, I had to find my rhythm and, you know,
所以我得先找到节奏
try to find my game.
找回自己的打法
So, we've been waiting just too many weeks
我们已经等了太多个星期
to say this to you in person.
才能当面说这句话
Cincinnati, the 2026 Wimbledon champion,
辛辛那提 有请温网冠军
Linda Noskova.
琳达·诺斯科娃
So, we all want to know the same thing.
我们都想知道同一件事
How much did you practice the dancing you
夺冠之后那支舞
had to do after you won the title?
你练了多久
I didn't think that you would ask me
没想到你会问
this, but I did not practice once,
这个 但我一次都没练过
so it was probably, you know, visible.
所以估计看得出来
I think that neither did Jannik.
我猜扬尼克也没练
So we had about the same experience
所以我俩的体验差不多
but it was fun you know it was cool.
但挺好玩的 挺酷的
A lot of people were preparing me
很多人提前给我打预防针
for this moment of the night.
说晚上会有这一出
I was not looking forward for it
我本来一点都不期待
but it was fun.
但真跳起来挺开心
All right. I'm going to accuse you
好 我要指控你
of something.
一件事
Last time you
上一次
and I talked maybe it was in Indian Wells
大概是在印第安维尔斯
and I was congratulating you
我恭喜你
on the season you're having and you said I
这个赛季打得好 而你说
don't feel like I've done anything.
我觉得我什么都没做成
You don't celebrate easily.
你不太会庆祝
How about now?
那现在呢
How are you feeling?
感觉怎么样
Congratulations
恭喜你
on the great season you're having.
这个赛季这么出色
I still don't know how to celebrate
我到现在还是不知道怎么庆祝
to be honest.
说老实话
I still have not probably 100% realized what
过去这几周发生的事
happened in the last couple of weeks.
我大概还没完全消化
You know, one would have thought I
按说
would gained such confidence,
我应该因此获得很大的信心
but I have not.
但并没有
So, it's still the same.
一切还是老样子
It's still tennis.
还是网球
The court is still the same.
球场还是那个球场
everything is, you know, nothing changed.
什么都没变
So, I had to get back and start, you know,
所以我得回来 重新开始
all over again like it never happened.
从头再来 像什么都没发生过
Well, one thing that's never changed
有一件事从来没变
is the fact that Cincinnati loves you.
就是辛辛那提爱你
Show some love
把掌声
for Grand Slam champion Linda Noskova.
送给大满贯冠军诺斯科娃